A Guide to the Laurance S. Rockefeller photographs, Snapshot Files, RG 4 FA1128C
Rockefeller Archive Center
Laurance S. Rockefeller photographs, Snapshot Files, RG 4
1920-1990
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller, Laurance Spelman
Rockefeller, Mary French
FA1128C
7.6 Cubic Feet 23 card file boxes (8" x 5" x 12")
Conditions Governing Access
Open for research with select materials restricted as noted. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC.
Arrangement
RG 4, LSR's Snapshot Files, is comprised of smaller format (up to 5"x 7") prints and some negatives, filed in photo envelopes. The files are arranged into seven series by subject and then by date, using the numerical system of subject categories employed by LSR's photo curators:
000 Art, 100 Family, 200 Houses, 300 Miscellaneous, 400 Civic, 500 Travel, 600 Resorts.
Each photo envelope (and the photos within it) was labeled with a six-digit number representing both the series or subject category and the envelope's filing order (e.g., envelope 100,017 contains family photos from the 1940s). Within a subject category, envelopes were, in principle, arranged in chronological order, though sometimes the numbers simply reflect the filing order. Photos later inserted into the arrangement received an additional sub-number (e.g., 100,017.1).
Scope and Contents
RG 4, LSR's Snapshot Files, contains LSR's personal photos, relating especially to his family, houses, friends and activities, travel, and resort developments. The Snapshot Files label reflects the smaller format of the prints (up to 5" x 7") and their grouping into discrete sets of prints and negatives, which are housed together in individual (and sometimes in their original) photo envelopes.
RG 4, which is also referred to as the 000,000+ series, contains numbered sets of smaller-format prints and negatives. Following the numerical system employed by LSR's photo curators, the Snapshot files are arranged into seven general subject categories:
000 Art, 100 Family, 200 Houses, 300 Miscellaneous, 400 Civic, 500 Travel, 600 Resorts.
Within each category the photos are further arranged by date and sometimes by subject. Each photo envelope (and the photos within it) is labeled with a six-digit number, representing the subject category, and the envelope's filing order (e.g., envelope 600,015 contains photos of Dorado Beach resort, 1956).
Devised around 1985, the filing system applied mostly to photos taken prior to that date. New photos seem to have been added only up until the late 1980s. The Snapshot Files arrangement brought order to a large portion of LSR's smaller-format print files, but it does not include all his "snapshots" or small-format images. There are several envelopes of snapshot photos as well as many individual smaller prints in LSR's Photo Files in RG 1 (FA1128).
Biographical / Historical
Laurance Spelman Rockefeller was born on May 26, 1910, in New York City, the fourth of the six children of John D. Rockefeller, Jr. and Abby Aldrich Rockefeller. He attended Lincoln School, a progressive coeducational preparatory school connected with Teachers College of Columbia University in New York City, before entering Princeton in 1928. A philosophy major, he graduated from Princeton in 1932 with a B.A. degree in philosophy and went on to two years of graduate study at Harvard Law School.
On August 15, 1934, Laurance Rockefeller married Mary French in the Congregational Church in Woodstock, Vermont. Together they raised three daughters and a son.
During World War II, Laurance Rockefeller served in the Navy (1942-1945), attaining the rank of lieutenant commander.
Laurance Rockefeller pursued a number of successful careers during his lifetime. He was a pioneer in the field of venture capital. He was a leading and influential figure for three decades in the American conservation movement. He led the development of one of the world's foremost cancer care and research facilities, and was both a benefactor and advisor to major educational institutions. And, with great foresight, he combined his personal vision for conservation, recreation, and the spiritual needs of individuals to develop internationally acclaimed environmentally oriented resorts. His many accomplishments have been recognized both nationally and internationally.
In 1935, he began working in the family office in Rockefeller Center. His first duties were to develop his knowledge and understanding of Rockefeller philanthropic activities, conservation projects, and business interests, through both study and playing a modest role in their operation. Simultaneously, he developed his own special interest, blending business acumen with the talents of a "gadgeteer," a label he once pinned on himself.
He became well known as an investor of risk capital in young enterprises whose future was based primarily on scientific and technological developments. Over the years his investment interests included the fields of aviation, aerospace, electronics, high temperature physics, composite materials, optics, lasers, data processing, thermionics, instrumentation, and nuclear power. Beginning in August 1969, his venture capital investments in these areas were made through a venture capital group, Venrock, formed by members of the Rockefeller family.
In a different area of venture capital, he developed outstanding environmentally oriented resort hotels in Puerto Rico, the Virgin Islands, Hawaii, and Vermont, serving as chairman of Rockresorts, Inc., a resort management company which he founded and chaired.
Conservation of the environment and recreational development constituted much of Laurance Rockefeller's philanthropy and public service. His introduction to public service came in 1939 when Governor Herbert H. Lehman of New York appointed him to the Palisades Interstate Park Commission (PIPC). He was president of the PIPC from 1970 to 1977 and continued as a commissioner until his resignation in December 1978. He was an advisor to Presidents Eisenhower, Kennedy, Johnson, Nixon, and Ford on matters of environmental conservation and outdoor recreation, and he worked on federal commissions set up to help develop national conservation and environmental policies and programs. In 1958, President Dwight D. Eisenhower appointed him chairman of the Outdoor Recreation Resources Review Commission (ORRRC), which charted ways of meeting the nation's outdoor recreation needs through the year 2000. He was a special emissary for President Lyndon Johnson in the effort that led to creation of the National Redwoods Park in California, and he served as chairman of President Nixon's Citizens' Advisory Committee on Environmental Quality, successor to a similar group which he headed under President Johnson. He played a pivotal role in the creation and development of several national parks including Grand Teton National Park in Wyoming, Virgin Islands National Park on the island of St. John, and Marsh-Billings-Rockefeller National Historical Park in Vermont.
He served as a leader of several important nonprofit and philanthropic organizations. He was president and later chairman of the Rockefeller Brothers Fund (1958-1980) and was a trustee of the Alfred P. Sloan Foundation (1960-1982). His first association with Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center in New York City was in 1947; he also served as chairman (1960-1982), overseeing an expansion and modernization of its operations. He was a longtime trustee of the New York Zoological Society (1935-1986) and served as its president (1969-1971) and chairman (1971-1985).
Laurance Rockefeller received many honors for his efforts on behalf of the environment and cancer research and treatment. Among them are the Alfred P. Sloan, Jr. Memorial Award from the American Cancer Society (1969), the Medal of Freedom (1969), Commander (Honorary) of the Most Excellent Order of the British Empire (1971), the Woodrow Wilson Award from Princeton University (1991), the Congressional Gold Medal (1991), the Chairman's Award from the National Geographic Society (1995), the Theodore Roosevelt National Park Medal of Honor (1995), and the Lady Bird Johnson Conservation Award for Lifetime Achievement (1997). In 2003, he became the first person to be made an honorary citizen of the British Virgin Islands in recognition of his many contributions to the area. In December 1959 he received the National Institute of Social Sciences' Gold Medal for distinguished services to humanity, an award previously bestowed upon his grandfather and father. This was the first time in the Institute's history that three generations of a family had been so honored. The citation to Laurance Rockefeller proclaimed him as a "creative organizer of ventures into new fields of human endeavor for the growing aspirations of mankind; [and a] leader in the conservation of natural resources and in the development of the medical and social sciences for the welfare of the individual." In 1967, the National Institute awarded Gold Medals to all five Rockefeller brothers in recognition of their individual and collective services to humanity.
Laurance Rockefeller died on July 11, 2004, at his home in Manhattan.
Prepared by Rockefeller Family and Associates, June 1982, and 2004.
Photographs
- Art (000), 1965-1989; 1
  - 000,000 Miscellaneous Art in houses, Undated (Box 1)
  - 000,001 834 Fifth Avenue, Room 5600, JY Ranch, 1965; 1986 (Box 1)
  - 000,002 Indian Art, Valley Ranch, 1983 (Box 1)
  - 000,003 Sold art (Box 1)
  - 000,004 Sculpture- "Girl on a Swing" at Pocantico, circa 1970 (Box 1)
  - 000,005 Sevres china plates, 1978 September (Box 1)
  - 000,006 834 Fifth Avenue, circa 1980 (Box 1)
  - 000,007 Indian Art- Wyoming Rugs, circa 1980s (Box 1)
  - 000,008 834 Fifth Avenue, circa 1982 (Box 1)
  - 000,009 Art in LSR Office, Room 5600, 1982 February (Box 1)
    Scope and Contents
    New Yorker for New York Award, 1981; ivory Mandarin figures and small duck.
  - 000,009.1 Sculpture- Pocantico, 1982 September (Box 1)
    Gerhard Marcks, "Maja."
  - 000,010 Mary French Rockefeller at 834 Fifth Avenue, 1982 October (Box 1)
  - 000,010.1 Buffalo Bill Museum, 1982-1983 (Box 1)
  - 000,010.2 Sculpture- Remington, 1983 March (Box 1)
    LSR and MFR with Leonard Firestone, Palm Springs. Frederic Remington bronzes (Coming through the Rye, Appeal to the Great Spirit). Includes negative strips and two disc negatives.
  - 000,010.3 Miscellaneous Art, 1983 April (Box 1)
  - 000,011 Portraits, circa 1983 (Box 1)
  - 000,012 Sculpture- France, circa 1982 or 1984 (Box 1)
  - 000,013 Sculpture- Central Park, 1985 April (Box 1)
  - 000,014 Sculpture- England (Box 1)
  - 000,015 Sculpture- France (Box 1)
  - 000,016 Sculpture- Pocantico, 1985 October (Box 1)
  - 000,017 834 Fifth Avenue, China Storeroom, 1987 November (Box 1)
- Family (100), 1920-1989; 2
  - 100,000 Miscellaneous LSR (Box 1)
  - 100,000.1 Trip to Europe and American West, 1923 (Box 1)
  - 100,001 Lincoln School, circa 1920-1925 (Box 1)
  - 100,002 Lincoln School, circa 1920-1925 (Box 1)
  - 100,003 Lincoln School, circa 1920-1925 (Box 1)
  - 100,004 Lincoln School, circa 1920-1925 (Box 1)
  - 100,005 Princeton, circa 1932 (Box 1)
  - 100,006 Novelty Postcards of LSR, 1927; undated (Box 1)
    Postcard photos of LSR in tuxedo drinking Champagne, July 1927, with note to friend (Samuel S); LSR as cancan dancer; unidentified photo of LSR at picnic on beach.
  - 100,006.1 Miscellaneous LSR, circa 1982; 1970s-1980s (Box 1)
  - 100,007 Lincoln School Reunion, 1940s- early 1950s (Box 1)
    Black and white group photo.
  - 100,008 Mary F. Rockefeller, early 1960s (Box 1)
    MFR skiing and in Library at 834 Fifth Ave.
  - 100,009 Mary F. Rockefeller, circa 1940s (Box 1)
    Includes image with Lenox Hill Group.
  - 100,010 Mary F. Rockefeller, 1950s-1980s (Box 1)
  - 100,011 Mary F. Rockefeller in Wyoming, 1963; 1980s (Box 1)
  - 100,011.1 Miscellaneous LSR and MFR, 1940s-1980s (Box 1)
  - 100,011.2 LSR and MFR, 1959 February (Box 1)
  - 100,011.3 LSR and MFR, 1964 March (Box 1)
  - 100,011.4 LSR and MFR, 1965 March (Box 1)
  - 100,011.5 LSR and MFR, 1965 June; 1967 October (Box 1)
    LSR and MFR at White House Conference on Natural Beauty
  - 100,011.6 LSR and MFR, 1971 (Box 1)
  - 100,011.65 LSR and MFR, 1983 June (Box 1)
  - 100,011.7 LSR and MFR anniversary, 1984 (Box 1)
    On church steps in Woodstock.
  - 100,011.8 LSR and MFR anniversary, 1984 August 15 (Box 1)
  - 100,011.9 LSR and MFR, circa 1985 December (Box 1)
  - 100,012 MFR family at Woodstock with French family and Hitchcocks, circa 1985 December (Box 1)
  - 100,013 MFR and children, circa 1938 (Box 1)
  - 100,014 Children, 1940s-1950s (Box 1)
  - 100,015 Children, 1940s (Box 1)
  - 100,016 Family at Kent House, 1930s-early 1950s (Box 1)
    MFR and LSR with babies and children; Kent House exteriors; Kent House construction. Includes small print and negative of LSR against tree at Phelps Lake, early 1950s.
  - 100,017 Daughters, 1940s (Box 1)
  - 100,018 Family, 1940s - early 1950s (Box 1)
    Children and MFR, young cousins, LSR and Larry in canoe, LSR speaking at unidentified event; toddler with nurse.
  - 100,019 Family, 1940s- early 1950s (Box 1)
    Family holiday party at 834 Fifth Ave apartment; children, Larry with toy car, MFR and Larry with unidentified baby. Laura.
  - 100,020 Children (Lucy, Larry), 1950s (Box 23)
    Conditions Governing Access
    Restricted. Material in the Rockefeller family collections that concerns the activities of living members of the Rockefeller family is restricted.
    Lucy on horseback, Lucy graduation, Larry riding, Larry in Wyoming.
  - 100,021 Laura Chasin- Graduation, 1954 (Box 1)
  - 100,022 Marion Weber- Graduation, 1956 (Box 23)
  - 100,022.1 Unidentified woman at Kent House, circa 1952 (Box 1)
  - 100,023 Lucy Waletzky, circa 1960; 1962 (Box 23)
  - 100,023.1 Marion Weber (Inuaugural Dinner of the Frederick Billings Society, Pacific School of Religion), 1989 (Box 1)
  - 100,024 Lucy Waletzky- Wedding, 1964 June 1965 (Box 23)
    Lucy's wedding to Charles Hamlin.
  - 100,025 Laura Chasin family, 1966 September (Box 23)
    Children in pool at Woodstock
  - 100,025.1 Marion Weber family, 1968 October (Box 23)
  - 100,025.5 Marion Weber family, 1970 (Box 23)
  - 100,026 Family, 1973 September (Box 2)
    LSR and family at JY Ranch; with Horace Albright; unidentified children and grandchildren.
  - 100,026.5 Family, 1978 December (Box 2)
    Polaroids - LSR family group photos.
  - 100,026.51 Lucy Waletzky Family - Thanksgiving, circa 1975 (Box 23)
  - 100,027 Laurance (Larry) Rockefeller, 1982 September 25 (Box 23)
    Wedding to Wendy Gordon.
  - 100,028 Laurance (Larry) Rockefeller, 1982 September 25 (Box 23)
  - 100,028.1 Laura Chasin family, 1982 February (Box 23)
    Case and Chasin children.
  - 100,029 Laurance (Larry) Rockefeller family - Catskills, 1984 (Box 23)
    Larry, Wendy, LSR, and MFR.
  - 100,030 Miscellaneous family, 1950s-1980s (Box 2)
    Snapshots - Thanksgiving and Christmas; Laura, 1984; black and white informal portraits of Lucy, Marion, Larry, James Case, and images of Phelps Lake, 1950s.
  - 100,030.1 Miscellaneous family, 1980s; 1985 September (Box 2)
    Laura at Woodstock, Dick Chasin, MFR, unidentified family and friends. Black and white prints.
  - 100,030.2 LSR Family Group Portrait, 1980 December (Box 2)
    Informal group photo with children and grandchildren.
  - 100,031 Children and Grandchildren, MFR family, circa 1975 - 1985 (Box 23)
  - 100,032 Rockefeller Brothers, 1926 - 1950 (Box 2)
    Postcard photo of David, Winthrop, and LSR on cutout donkey, "On Our Honey Moon," 1926; Winthrop in army uniform, 1941; LSR, JDR Jr., and DR on horseback, early 1930s; Saturday Evening Post photos of 4 brothers and of DR at Pocantico, 1950.
  - 100,032.1 JDR Jr. and AAR in motorcar (Box 2)
  - 100,033 JDR Jr. (Box 2)
    Formal dinner at Pocantico. 1 image.
  - 100,034 David, 1940 September 7; September 1980 (Box 2)
    Wedding (proof prints); family at St. Barts
  - 100,035 Rockefeller Family, circa 1950s (Box 2)
    Formal dinner at Pocantico. LSR, WR, MFR with hair up.
  - 100,036 LSR and Happy Rockefeller, 1970s-1980s (Box 2)
    Formal occasion, with one inidentified woman.
  - 100,037 Rockefeller Family, 1930s (Box 2)
    JDR Sr. with Marilyn, Mitzi, and Rodman, JDR Jr., AAR, and NA; LSR with Babs; JDR Jr. and AAR driving carriage.
  - 100,038 Family Wedding in Maine, 1980s (Box 2)
    DR family wedding; LSR and MFR in Vermont.
  - 100,039 Armstrong Ranch, circa 1948 (Box 2)
    Nelson, Winthrop, Tod, Tom Armstrong, and others. Armstrong Ranch, Kingsville, TX.
  - 100,040 Armstrong Ranch, 1948 (Box 2)
    Color slides.
  - 100,041 Family, circa late 1940s - 1950 May (Box 2)
    Rockefeller family gatherings at Pocantico; MFR with Larry; daughter with camera; MFR and Babs; image of Lucy Truman Aldrich; MFR and Elizabeth French Hitchcock; Dauntless. Includes set of 8 negatives that do not match prints in the file (unidentified couple, girl with braids, in Caribbean or Florida). Negatives are stored separately in box 24.
    Appraisal
    Ten badly deteriorating negatives have been removed from the file and have been deaccessioned. There are corresponding prints in the file for all of the negative images. (One of the prints - of LSR and Babs - is found in envelope 100,037 instead.)
  - 100,042 Rockefeller Family Christmas Party, 1954 December 25 (Box 2)
    Prints and negatives (marked for enlargements).
    Separated Materials
    Negatives are stored separately in box 24.
  - 100,043 Family, 1954-1955 (Box 2)
    Small prints and negatives- Family Christmas party at 1 Beekman Place (Abby Mauze's), 1954, and at 834 Fifth Ave, 1955; negatives, LSR at 5600 Rockefeller Center office, Reaction Motors models, October 1955.
    Negatives (4 sets) are stored separately in box 24.
  - 100,044 Ann Rockefeller Wedding, 1955 June 25 (Box 23)
    Small prints and negatives.
    Negatives (in two envelopes) are stored separately in box 24.
  - 100,045 Rockefeller Family Christmas Party, 1954 December 25 (Box 2)
    Prints.
  - 100,046 Rockefeller Family Christmas Party, 1957 December 25 (Box 2)
    Hosted by NAR.
  - 100,047 Dr. I. McGrath Wedding, Hudson Pines, 1959 October 31 (Box 2)
    File consists entirely of negatives.
    Negatives (in 4 sets, A-D) are stored separately in box 24.
  - 100,048 Rockefeller Family Christmas Party, 1959 December 25 (Box 2)
    At Abby Mauze's, 1 Beekman Place. Negatives only.
    Negatives (2 envelopes) have been separated to box 24.
  - 100,049 Mary Clark Rockefeller Wedding, 1961 March 18 (Box 23)
    Prints and negatives.
  - 100,050 Rockefeller Family Christmas Party, 1963 December 25 (Box 2)
    Negatives (2 envelopes) are stored separately in box 24.
  - 100,051 Rockefeller Family Christmas Party, 1965 December 25 (Box 2)
    Hosted by NAR. Includes two images of six Rockefeller siblings reviewing Kykuit plans.
    Negatives (2 envelopes, A-C and D-F) are stored separately in box 24.
  - 100,052 LSR and DR at Rockefeller Center, 1984 June 11 (Box 2)
    Two images - one with MFR and Peggy R.
  - 100,053 Larry Rockefeller family, 1985 September (Box 23)
  - 100,054 Larry Rockefeller family, 1985 December (Box 23)
    Includes LSR and MFR.
  - 100,055 Larry Rockefeller family, 1986 March (Box 23)
    In Catskills.
  - 100,056 Larry Rockefeller family, 1986 March (Box 23)
    LSR and MFR with baby. Prints and disc negative.
  - 100,057 David and Peggy Rockefeller 45th Anniversary, 1985 September (Box 2)
    At JY Ranch. Includes image of LSR and MFR.
  - 100,058 MFR, 1986 April (Box 2)
  - 100,059 Laura Chasin 50th Birthday Celebration, 1986 October 11 (Box 2)
    Woodstock, VT. Color prints and disc negative. File also includes 5x7 photos of Laura and LSR at dedication of LSR Board Room, Rockefeller Research Laboratories, 1989 May 11, and of LSR and Larry R. at Phelps Lake.
  - 100,060 Rockefeller Family Cemetery and Japanese House, 1987 May 30 (Box 2)
    Negatives and one color print.
  - 100,061 MFR and Floral Arrangements, 1986 June (Box 2)
    MFR after hip operation. Images mainly of flower arrangements she received.
  - 100,062 Lucy Waletzky, MFR, 1988 April (Box 2)
    At Pocantico with Larry R. and unidentified man. Scenic views. Artwork at 834 Fifth Ave. Color prints and negatives.
  - 100,063 Lincoln School Reunion, 1988 June 2 (Box 3)
    New York cruise aboard the Imperator. Three small albums of color snapshots, plus a few loose photos.
  - 100,063.1 Lincoln School Reunion, 1988 June 2 (Box 3)
    New York cruise. Three small albums of color snapshots.
  - Separated Negatives (Box 24)
    Negatives separated from Series 100 snapshot files: from envelopes 100,041; 100,042; 100,043 (4 sets); 100,044 (2 sets); 100,046; 100,047 (4 sets, A-D); 100,048 (2 sets); 100,049; 100,050 (2 sets); 100,051 (2 sets, A-E).
- Houses (200), 1930-1994; 3
  - 200,000 House on water, 1956 October 1 (Box 3)
    Possibly Fisher's Island house?
  - 200,001 Unidentified house, 1983 April (Box 3)
    Photos of fabric swatches and wallpaper for redecorating unidentified house. Prints and disc negative.
  - 200,002 James H. and Laura R. Case House, Van Hornesville, NY, 1962-1963 (Box 3)
    Construction photos. Includes one image of James Case.
  - 200,003 New York, circa 1974 (Box 3)
    Pine tree at Rockwood Hall (LSR Christmas card image); view of Central Park zoo from 834 Fifth Ave.
  - 200,003.9 834 Fifth Ave, 1978 January 20 (Box 3)
    Snow on terrace.
  - 200,004 Pocantico views, Caribbean, 1978 June (Box 3)
    Prints and slides.
  - 200,005 Pocantico, 1979 October (Box 3)
    Views
  - 200,006 Kykuit, circa 1980s (Box 3)
    LSR, DR, MFR, hosting dinner for foreign visitors. Includes views of basement art gallery.
  - 200,007 Kent House winter views, 1980-1981 (Box 3)
  - 200,008 Pocantico, circa 1980s (Box 3)
    Pool and sculpture.
  - 200,009 Japan Trip, 1980 December (Box 3)
    File, miscategorized, contains images from Japan trip; one image of LSR, MFR, and others, standing before sculpture.
  - 200,010 834 Fifth Avenue - Artwork, 1981 (Box 3)
  - 200,011 Pocantico, 1981 June (Box 3)
    Sculpture, gardens, views. See also 200,014.
  - 200,012 Pocantico, 1981 June (Box 3)
    Tarrytown Lakes, views, Stone Barns, Marymount properties, Kent House and MFR.
  - 200,013 Kykuit, 1981 July (Box 3)
  - 200,014 Pocantico, 1981 July (Box 3)
    Kykuit grounds and Stone Barns. Includes duplicates of images in 200,011.
  - 200,015 834 Fifth Ave and Pocantico, circa 1982 (Box 3)
    John French birthday party; new pool house, Pocantico.
  - 200,016 New York, 1982 July (Box 3)
    Flowers, New York views. Includes disc negative.
  - 200,016.1 Pocantico, 1982 (Box 3)
    Pool house; Kykuit sculpture and grillwork. Includes 2 disc negatives.
  - 200,017 Pocantico and Woodstock, 1983 (Box 3)
    Rockefeller Family cemetery; automobiles in Carriage House; LSR and daughters at Kent House; Billings Farm and Museum.
  - 200,018 Kykuit Partition Formal Closing, 1983 December 7 (Box 3)
    Two images.
  - 200,019 New York, 1984 January (Box 3)
  - 200,020 Woodstock, 1985 January (Box 3)
  - 200,020.1 Pocantico Maps, 1990 (Box 3)
    Property, trails, park evolution, etc.
  - 200,021 Ronald and Nancy Reagan visit to Pocantico, 1986 July (Box 3)
    Includes some unidentified landscape views, 1957.
  - 200,021a Kykuit views, 1994 (Box 3)
    Photos by Mary Louise Pierson.
  - 200,021.1 Woodstock, 1950s; undated (Box 4)
    LSR and MFR at horse show; MFR golfing; LSR with binoculars.
  - 200,022 Woodstock - Overhead Wires, 1971 (Box 4)
  - 200,023 Woodstock and New York, 1974 Fall (Box 4)
    Family at Woodstock Mansion; Billings Farm; French family reunion; New York river views.
  - 200,023a Woodstock, 1978 (Box 4)
    Billings Farm, family.
  - 200,023b New York - East River Boat Ride, 1974 October (Box 4)